<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wiimmfi</string>
    <string name="github">All of the code in this project is open source on my GitHub repository <a href='https://github.com/brysonsteck/wiimmfi-watcher/tree/master'>here.</a> You are free to use this code and expand upon it under the GNU General Public License.</string>
    <string name="bugs">Speaking of bugs, did you find a bug? First, make sure that the issue you found is not listed on my <a href='https://github.com/brysonsteck/wiimmfi-watcher/blob/master/TODO.md'>todo list.</a> It\'s possible I\'m already aware of it or working on it. If your issue is not addressed on the todo list, then you can create an issue on my GitHub repository <a href='https://github.com/brysonsteck/wiimmfi-watcher/issues'>here.</a> If you don\'t know how to use GitHub, you can fill out this <a href='https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSd6qCONAP2tsbHPgzu_CdZcHVHL5nx7q0XFqrVfExEc84kqUQ/viewform?usp=sf_link'>Google Form</a> instead.</string>
    <string name="license">&#169; Copyright 2021 Bryson Steck\n\nWiimmfi Watcher is available under the GNU General Public License Version 3. You can view the license <a href='https://github.com/brysonsteck/wiimmfi-watcher/tree/dev/LICENSE'>here.</a>\n\nWiimmfi Watcher is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
    it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
    the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
    (at your option) any later version.\n\nWiimmfi Watcher is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
    but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
    MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
    GNU General Public License for more details.\n\nYou should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
    along with Wiimmfi Watcher.  If not, see &lt;<a href='https://www.gnu.org/licenses/'>https://www.gnu.org/licenses/</a>&gt;.</string>
    <string name="contact">If you would like to get ahold of me for any reason unrelated to bug reports or this app in general, you can contact me through email at <a href='mailto:steck.bryson@gmail.com'>steck.bryson@gmail.com</a> or on Discord at bryzinga#9971.</string>
</resources>